<chapter id="chapters.multiglide">
  <chapterinfo>
    <date>$Date$</date>
  </chapterinfo>

  <indexterm><primary>multi-glide</primary></indexterm>
  <title>Multi-Glider Support</title>

  <section id="chapters.multiglide.introduction">
		  <title>Introduction</title>
		  
		  <para>
		  JGlideMon has the ability to connect to more than one instance
		  of Glider without having to install a separate copy of JGlideMon
		  and start another instance. This also means that you only have
		  to have one copy of the Java Virtual Machine running, which
		  results in less overall memory usage. 
  		  </para>

		  <para>
				  Before going into the details of configuring multiple Glider
				  connections, some terminology needs to be addressed.
				  For simplicity's sake, think of Glider as a server. After all, that
				  is exactly what Glider is doing with regard to the remote connection.
		  </para>
  </section>

  <section id="chapters.multiglide.procedure">
		  <title>Procedure</title>

		  <para>
				  You should already have one server configured. The configuration dialog was
				  displayed the first time you ran JGlideMon. If you upgraded from an older
				  version, your old settings were converted to the "Default" server settings.
		  </para>
		  <para>
				  To add an additional server, click "Add New Server..." from the "Servers" menu.

				  <screenshot>
						  <screeninfo>Add New Server</screeninfo>
						  <imageobject>
							  <imagedata fileref="images/chapters/multiglide/add_new.jpg" format="JPG" />
						  </imageobject>
				  </screenshot>
		  </para>
		  <para>
				  You will be prompted to enter the connection information and the configuration dialog
				  will be opened. Enter the required information as you did for the first server. See
				  <link linkend="chapters.config">the configuration chapter</link> for more details. It
				  is necessary for you to enter a unique name for each server. This name helps identify
				  which JGlideMon window is which when you start having several windows open.
		  </para>
		  <para>
				  Assuming your connection information is correct and Glider is running, you should now
				  be connecting to your second instance of Glider.
		  </para>
  </section>

  <section id="chapters.multiglide.control">
		  <title>Control</title>

		  <para>
				  To start with, you can quickly switch between JGlideMon windows via
				  "Servers->Activate Server...". The "Activate Server..." sub-menu lists
				  all of the servers you have configured JGlideMon to connect to. This is
				  where the name you give a server helps you distinguis which window you want
				  to view. Clicking on a name (or using the accelerator key CTRL-ALT-##) will
				  maximize that server's window, if necessary, and bring it to the foreground.
		  </para>
		  <para>
				  For conveinance, the "Connect All Servers" and "Disconnect All Servers" options
				  are available in the "Servers" menu to quickly connect or disconnect each Glider
				  connection as if you had gone to each JGlideMon window and manually clicked the
				  "Connect" or "Disconnect" button. 
		  </para>
		  <para>
				  If you no longer need to connect to a particular Glider instance, you can click
				  "Remove Current Server" from the "Servers" menu from the JGlideMon window of the
				  server you want to remove. This will close the window and all settings for the
				  particular connection <emphasis>will be deleted</emphasis>. It will not reappear
				  when JGlideMon is restarted.
		  </para>
		  <note>
				  <para>
						  You cannot remove a server if there is only one configured.
				  </para>
		  </note>
		  <para>
				  If you would like to temporarily remove a server's window but retain its
				  settings so that you can connect to it at some point in the future, you can
				  put the server in an "inactive" state by closing its window via "File->Exit"
				  or pressing the X in the upper right and clicking "No" on the dialog that 
				  appears.

				  <screenshot>
						  <screeninfo>Do you want to exit?</screeninfo>
						  <imageobject>
							  <imagedata fileref="images/chapters/multiglide/suspend.jpg" format="JPG" />
						  </imageobject>
				  </screenshot>
		  </para>
		  <para>
				  Once a server is deactivated, it will not reappear, even when JGlideMon is restarted,
				  until you explicity reactivate it. In order to reactivate an inactive server, click
				  its name via "Servers->Activate Server...". You will notice that there is a red light
				  next to its name to indicate its inactive status. Previously it was green. For conveinance,
				  you can activate all inactive servers at once by cicking "Servers->Activate Inactive Servers".
		  </para>
  </section>

  <section id="chapters.multiglide.screenshotcontrol">
		  <title>Screenshot Control</title>

		  <para>
				  If you need to connect to multiple Glider instances, it is likely that you are running
				  some of the instances on the same computer. In this case, it is useful to be able to
				  control the WoW window state. There are several features to aid with this.
		  </para>
		  <para>
				  For any particular server, you can quickly make its WoW window the foreground window
				  so that screenshots will not have any other windows on top of the window you actually 
				  want to see. The simplest command is to just restore and activate the WoW window.
				  If the WoW window is hidden or shrunk, it will be restored to regular size and 
				  activated so that it is the top-most window. This command is available via
				  "Screenshot->Shrink/Restore->Restore and Activate Window".
		  </para>
		  <note>
				  <para>
						  It seems that sometimes Glider may restore the WoW window but it does not
						  get activated and other windows still appear on top. Simply clicking
						  the option to restore the window again should fix it.
				  </para>
		  </note>
		  <para>
				  In addition to simply restoring the window, you can restore the current window and
				  shrink or hide the other server's respective WoW windows by the approriate commands
				  in "Screenshot->Shrink/Restore".
		  </para>
		  <para>
				  For completeness, commands to shrink or hide the current or all WoW windows are also
				  available.
		  </para>
  </section>
</chapter>
