<section id="chapters.installation.procedure">
  <sectioninfo>
    <date>$Date$</date>
  </sectioninfo>

  <indexterm><primary>installation</primary><secondary>procedure</secondary></indexterm>
  <title>Procedure</title>
  
  <para>
		  JGlideMon is distributed as a zip file named something like <filename>JGlideMon_core_vX.X.YYY.zip</filename>.
		  X.X refers to the major version number. This number increases when there are signicant changes
		  or additions to JGlideMon. YYY refers to the revision number. JGlideMon uses version control
		  software called Subversion. This helps track changes and saves copies of older version of code
		  in case something breaks and it needs to be reverted. The revision number is Subversion's internal
		  version of JGlideMon. It increases whenever a change (large or small) is commited. It is possible
		  that a version of JGlideMon will be released with the same major version number but different
		  revision numbers. This would occur when a bug has been fixed or something minor has change.
  </para>

  <para>
		  After you have downloaded the core zip file, you must extract it to a folder. It does not
		  matter where this folder is or what it is named but you should make it something
		  meaningful, say <filename>C:\Program Files\JGlideMon</filename>. 
  </para>

  <para>
		  For optional components, like text-to-speech, simply extract the zip file into the
		  same folder that JGlideMon has been installed to. It is safe to overrite any
		  files or folders if you are prompted to do so.
  </para>

  <para>
		  JGlideMon is also distributed as an installer file for Windows. Simply launch the installer
		  and follow the wizard. If a version of JGlideMon is installed (that was previously installed
		  with an installer) it will be upgraded to the new version. If Java is not installed, you will be
		  prompted to download and install it.
  </para>

  <para>
		  In order to launch JGlideMon, simply double-click on <filename>JGlideMon.jar</filename>. For conveinance on Windows,
		  you can right-click on <filename>JGlideMon.jar</filename> and click "Send To->Desktop (create shortcut)". If you prefer
		  to start JGlideMon from the command line, you must invoke it like:
		  <screen>
				  <prompt>C:\&gt;</prompt> <command>cd path\to\JGlideMon\Folder</command>
				  <prompt>C:\path\to\JGlideMon\folder\&gt;</prompt> <command>java -jar JGlideMon.jar</command>
		  </screen>
  </para>
  <para>
		  When you launch JGlideMon for the first time, you will be prompted to enter the network settings to connect
		  to Glider. At this point you can configure other settings as you like.
		  For further details, see <link linkend="chapters.config">the configuration chapter</link>.
  </para>
</section>
