<section id="chapters.interface.tabs.chat">
  <sectioninfo>
    <date>$Date$</date>
  </sectioninfo>

  <indexterm><primary>chat</primary><secondary>tab</secondary></indexterm>
  <title>Chat Tab</title>
  
  <para>
		  The Chat Tab allows you to review all chat log entries that have
		  occured since you connected to Glider. They are colored similarly
		  to how they appear in-game to make it easier to pick out lines
		  of interest.
  </para>

  <screenshot>
		  <screeninfo>Chat Tab</screeninfo>
		  <imageobject>
				  <imagedata fileref="images/chapters/interface/chat_tab.jpg" format="JPG" />
		  </imageobject>
  </screenshot>


  <para>
		  The following sub-tabs help by separating specific types
		  of chat:

		  <itemizedlist>
				  <listitem>All Chat</listitem>
				  <listitem>Public Chat</listitem>
				  <listitem>Whisper/Say/Yell</listitem>
				  <listitem>Guild</listitem>
		  </itemizedlist>
  </para>

  <section id="chapters.interface.tabs.chat.sendchat">
		  <indexterm><primary>send</primary><secondary>chat</secondary></indexterm>
		  <title>Sending Chat</title>

		  <para>
				  From the bottom of this tab, you can send chat. In order to
				  do so, you must select the type of message you wish to send.
				  The options are:
				  <itemizedlist>
						  <listitem>Whisper</listitem>
						  <listitem>Reply</listitem>
						  <listitem>Say</listitem>
						  <listitem>Guild</listitem>
						  <listitem>Raw</listitem>
				  </itemizedlist>
		  </para>
		  <para>
				  When sending a whisper, a smaller textbox appears for
				  you to enter the recipient's name.
		  </para>
		  <tip>
				  <para>
						  You can double click on a line of chat that is from another player,
						  i.e. a whisper from them, or a line where they said something in
						  any channel, and their name will be filled into the whisper to
						  textbox.
				  </para>
		  </tip>
		  <para>
				  Type your message in the large textbox and press "Send" or
				  the Enter key. Your message will be queued and sent.
		  </para>
		  <caution>
				  <para>
						  Do <emphasis>not</emphasis> add a slash or a vertical bar unless
						  you are using the "Raw" type. They will be added automatically 
						  for you. If you are using "Raw", a vertical bar (|) will
						  represent an Enter keystroke and #VK# will represent a
						  keystroke with a virtual key code number of VK. #13#
						  is another way to indicate an Enter keystroke.
				  </para>
		  </caution>
		  <note>
				  <para>
						  Glider is limited to pressing individual keys as if on
						  a keyboard. It can only send one keystroke at a time. This
						  means that it cannot send anything that would require you
						  to hold down the shift key, namely uppercase letters,
						  most punctuation, and foreign characters. This also implies
						  that you cannot send whispers to people who have special
						  characters in their name.
				  </para>
		  </note>
		  <tip>
				  <para>
						  If you wish to say something in a public chat channel or
						  to send an emote, select Guild or Say as the type and then
						  for these cases you <emphasis>should</emphasis> add the slash command.
				  </para>
		  </tip>
		  <para>
				  When JGlideMon sends chat, it first stops Glider, pauses, sends
				  an Enter keystroke, pauses, sends the slash command, pauses, and
				  finally sends the rest of the message. These pauses have been added
				  to overcome Glider's difficulty in sending one long message at once.
				  While JGlideMon is very reliable at sending the message to the proper
				  channel, i.e. actually whispering someone instead of saying
				  "r person message", the last couple of characters sometimes get cut
				  off. This is an issue with Glider.
		  </para>
		  <tip>
				  <para>
						  To help overcome the last couple of characters sometimes getting
						  cut off, try appending several spaces or periods to your message.
				  </para>
		  </tip>
  </section>
</section>
