<section id="chapters.interface.tabs.screenshot">
  <sectioninfo>
    <date>$Date$</date>
  </sectioninfo>

  <indexterm><primary>screenshot</primary><secondary>tab</secondary></indexterm>
  <title>Screenshot Tab</title>
  
  <para>
		  The screenshot will be updated in accordance with the
		  <link linkend="chapters.config.screenshot">screenshot settings</link>.
		  In order to reduce bandwidth, the screenshot will only be updated
		  if the screenshot tab is the current tab or if the built-in
		  webserver is running. When the screenshot is being updated,
		  the status bar at the bottom of the window is updated to 
		  indicate the current progress. You can manually force an immediate
		  update of the screenshot by selecting "Refresh Screenshot Immediately"
		  from the "Screenshot" menu or by pressing F5.
  </para>

  <note>
		  <para>
				  Screenshots only work when Glider is attached to WoW.
		  </para>
  </note>

  <section id="chapters.interface.tabs.screenshot.sendkeys">
		  <indexterm><primary>keys</primary><secondary>mouse</secondary></indexterm>
		  <title>Sending Keystrokes and Mouse Clicks</title>

	  <para>
		  In addition to displaying the screenshot itself, you can send keystrokes and
		  mouse clicks to Glider while this tab is active. In order to do either, you must
		  first enable that option via the "Screenshots" menu and selecting 
		  "Enable Sending Keystrokes" or by pressing Alt+K. This setting will always be disabled when
		  JGlideMon is started in order to prevent accidental key sending.
	  </para>

  <screenshot>
		  <screeninfo>Enable Sending Keystrokes</screeninfo>
		  <imageobject>
				  <imagedata fileref="images/chapters/interface/enable_keystrokes.jpg" format="JPG" />
		  </imageobject>
  </screenshot>

	  <para>
			  Next, to send a keystroke, simply start pressing keys as if you were actually
			  playing WoW. If you press the C key, your character info pane will appear.
	  </para>
	  <para>
			  To send mouse clicks, simply click on the screenshot image. Right and left
			  clicking both work. You can, for example, press the N key, then click to 
			  spend talent points.
	  </para>
	  <note>
			  <para>
					  Mouse clicks only work while Glider is actively running a profile.
					  This is a limitation of Glider.
			  </para>
	  </note>
  </section>
</section>
