<section id="chapters.interface.tabs.urgent">
  <sectioninfo>
    <date>$Date$</date>
  </sectioninfo>

  <indexterm><primary>urgent</primary><secondary>tab</secondary></indexterm>
  <title>Urgent Tab</title>
  
  <para>
		  The urgent tab will contain information that you may find particularly
		  important. 
  </para>

  <section id="chapters.interface.tabs.urgent.log">
		  <indexterm><primary>log</primary><secondary>tab</secondary></indexterm>
		  <title>Log Sub-Tab</title>

		  <para>
				  This tab will contain log entries that you should be made aware of.
				  An entry will appear here when you are whispered, when someone
				  says something nearby, when you are being followed, when you die,
				  as well as any log entry from Glider that starts with an exclamation
				  point (!) or an asterisk (*).
		  </para>

  <screenshot>
		  <screeninfo>Urgent Log Tab</screeninfo>
		  <imageobject>
				  <imagedata fileref="images/chapters/interface/urgent_log_tab.jpg" format="JPG" />
		  </imageobject>
  </screenshot>

		  <para>
				  Some log entries, such as whispers and follower alerts will play the
				  appropriate sound when they are received. See <link linkend="chapters.config.sound">Sound Settings</link>
				  if you would like to disable sounds. Whenever any urgent log entry is
				  added, this tab will automatically be selected.
		  </para>
  </section>

  <section id="chapters.interface.tabs.urgent.followers">
		  <indexterm><primary>followers</primary><secondary>tab</secondary></indexterm>
		  <title>Followers Sub-Tab</title>

		  <para>
				  This tab displays a table that tracks when Glider says "New friend: XXX",
				  "Removing friend: XXX", and "Being followed by XXX". It may be useful
				  to know if someone has caused a follower alert multiple times.
		  </para>

  <screenshot>
		  <screeninfo>Urgent Followers Tab</screeninfo>
		  <imageobject>
				  <imagedata fileref="images/chapters/interface/urgent_followers_tab.jpg" format="JPG" />
		  </imageobject>
  </screenshot>

		  <table>
				  <title>Follower Table Columns</title>
				  <tgroup cols="2" align="left" colsep="1" rowsep="1">
						  <thead>
								  <row>
										  <entry>Column</entry>
										  <entry>Description</entry>
								  </row>
						  </thead>
						  <tbody>
								  <row>
										  <entry>Last Seen</entry>
										  <entry>This is the time that Glider last saw this person, either adding, removing, or following.</entry>
								  </row>
								  <row>
										  <entry>Last Event</entry>
										  <entry>This is what was occuring when Glider last saw this person.
												  <itemizedlist>
														  <listitem>"Adding" indicates that this person has come near your character but has not been in your area for your follower alert time.</listitem>
														  <listitem>"Following" indicates that this person has been near your character for at least as long as your follower alert time.</listitem>
														  <listitem>"Removing" indicates that this person has left your character's vicinity.</listitem>
												  </itemizedlist>
										  </entry>
								  </row>
								  <row>
										  <entry># Encounters</entry>
										  <entry>This is the number of times that the same person has come within your character's vicinity but not nessarily followed you.</entry>
								  </row>
								  <row>
										  <entry># Follow Alerts</entry>
										  <entry>This is the number of times that the same person has triggered Glider's follower alert. If this is very high, it could potentially indicate the person is following you intentionally.</entry>
								  </row>
								  <row>
										  <entry>Name</entry>
										  <entry>This is the name of the person. Note that it may be "(unknown)" when Glider is unable to determine the person's name.</entry>
								  </row>
								  <row>
										  <entry>ID</entry>
										  <entry>This is the ID of the person that Glider reports, if available.</entry>
								  </row>
								  <row>
										  <entry>Race/Class</entry>
										  <entry>This is the race and class of the person, if available.</entry>
								  </row>
						  </tbody>
				  </tgroup>
		  </table>
  </section>
</section>
